♪If I am gone from this world,
will the dark night collapse?♪
♪If I never return
to guard by your side♪
♪If I seal away our encounter
and erase all trace♪
♪Like endless snow
falling into the deep sea♪
♪This life is but a fleeting illusion,
yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪
=Spring Over Phoenix Pond=
(Adapted from Qin An'an's
"Spring Over Phoenix Pond")
=Episode 3=
(Marquis Yongping Residence)
Here, Prince Jing.
Please give this a try.
Try this.
Your Highness,
you must have been startled
when you arrived today.
I
would like to propose a toast
to you on my father's behalf.
The Marquis has already
dealt with the matter,
so there's no need for you to worry.
I've had a bit too much to drink,
so I'll head back to rest now.
Then...
Just finish this cup.
Alright.
Take care, Your Highness.
Alright, please stay.
Take care.
Take care, Your Highness.
(With Xiao Yunting's
tolerance for alcohol,)
(there's no way
he'd get drunk so easily.)
(What is he up to?)
(He clearly went into the study.)
(Where is he?)
(Why is Young Lady Qi)
(following me for no reason?)
(Model Sayings)
Can you see clearly?
What are you looking for, Your Highness?
I'll help you look.
(He probably
didn't find anything, right?)
I'm not good with alcohol.
I lost my way on the path back
and wandered in here by mistake.
How rude of me.
Not at all.
It is our lack of proper care.
I would be honored to show you
the way back, Your Highness.
Why is the door
to the Marquis's study open?
This is a restricted area
in the residence.
No one is allowed to trespass.
Go check it out quickly.
(He really is looking
for the account book.)
(The Qi family's survival
depends on this account book.)
(Prince Qi hasn't been
brought down yet,)
(so the Qi family's trump card
cannot be broken yet.)
(Xiao Yunting,)
(I can't give you
the account book just yet.)
The Marquis must have
forgotten to close the door.
Let's go.
Alright.
I'm sorry.
It was an emergency just now,
so please forgive my offense.
It's fine.
You should go back
and rest early, Your Highness.
I'll lead the way for you.
Regarding today's matter...
I won't say a word to anyone.
After you.
Zhao,
are you alright?
Put on the kneepads
so that kneeling won't hurt as much.
It's all my fault.
This has nothing to do with you.
Jin,
no matter what,
I won't let you be mistreated.
If not for her,
you'd be living comfortably
in Mingyue Pavilion.
Sister is the legitimate daughter
of the Marquis Residence,
so by rights, she ought
to live in Mingyue Pavilion.
It is I, an outsider...
She laid a hand on you?
No,
I was just careless myself.
Jin,
rest assured,
everyone in Mingyue Pavilion
is my person.
I will help you drive her away.
Your Highness,
you're finally back!
What took so long?
Was there some mishap?
I ran into Young Lady Qi in the study,
so it wasn't convenient to investigate.
How about on your end?
I went to search the accounting room,
but I didn't find anything either.
Since we didn't get the evidence,
we'll keep searching.
Prince Qi is greedy and tyrannical,
causing misery for the people.
For the sake of the people under heaven,
I must bring him down.
Besides,
from what I saw today,
Qi Yuan's situation
in the Qi family is awkward.
They are not united in heart.
Your Highness wants
to win her over and use her?
Young Lady Qi sure has some skill.
Look at those two slaps she delivered.
If we could really
recruit her into our ranks,
wouldn't that be...
She is indeed quite interesting.
She can be useful to me.
(Mingyue Pavilion)
- Welcome back, Young Lady.
Serve the tea.
I am thirsty.
You just returned here, Young Lady,
so you probably
don't know the rules here yet.
Tea and refreshments
are served at set times.
They aren't available whenever you want.
Nanny Zhang,
I grew up in an estate.
I don't understand complex principles.
I only know one truth.
Whose bread you eat,
whose rules you follow.
I am foolish,
and only recognize
one master in this residence.
Yes...
Yes.
I will go fetch tea
for you now, Young Lady.
I will get you the finest tea
in the residence.
Lianqiao,
I heard your mother is gravely ill.
Take this,
and hire a good physician.
Thank you, Young Lady!
I will remain faithful
to you all my life,
without a second thought.
Young Lady,
this is the wound medicine I just got.
Apply it to your leg now.
You wretched wench!
How dare you steal medicine
meant for the master?
I'll beat you to death!
(Lianqiao,)
(in my past life, you were
the only one good to me,)
- (yet I dragged you into punishment.)
- I'll beat you to death!
(In this life, I will protect you.)
(Lianqiao, Qi Yuan's maidservant)
Is it delicious?
Eat more.
Qi Yuan.
Qi Yuan!
Where is Qi Yuan?
Qi Yuan,
why did you harm your brother?
Sit down.
I do not know
what wrong I have committed.
You still dare to deny it?
You...
- Dear.
- Madam.
You have gone out of line!
I do not know
what wrong I have committed.
Please explain it clearly,
Father and Mother.
You almost caused Zhao to lose his life,
and you're still putting on an act here?
He almost lost his life,
and I caused it?
You...
I haven't even been to his room.
May I ask how I could have harmed him?
Young Lady secretly made a doll
to curse the Young Master.
That is why he became so critically ill.
Is that so?
You want to condemn me
based solely on her word?
What else do I have to say?
Where is the doll
you claimed to see?
It is right under
the big tree in the courtyard.
I saw it with my own eyes
when Young Lady buried it there.
Dig it all up for me!
Do you think Young Lady Qi
can settle this matter?
The way I see it,
she has the strength of a butcher,
but not necessarily
the ability to deal
with inner residence schemes.
It seems it will be hard
for her to help us.
No rush.
Let's wait and see
how things develop first.
Hurry and bring it out.
Master, Madam,
this is it.
Nanny Zhang,
are you sure there is voodoo inside?
I am certain.
Don't even think
about denying it, Young Lady.
Where is the doll you spoke of?
Didn't you say there
was something inside?
This...
This is all liquor.
The Eldest Princess
loves the liquor I brew,
so I brewed extra
to keep as a collection.
I never thought it
would end up harming my brother.
The Eldest Princess?
Nanny Zhang,
are you playing us for fools here?
I really saw it with my own eyes.
Fool.
Young Lady,
didn't you tell me
to keep an eye on Nanny Zhang?
Today, I saw her acting suspiciously,
burying this jar in
(Qi Zhao)
the northeast corner of the courtyard.
I dug it up while she wasn't looking,
and inside was actually
this voodoo doll.
Her scheme is nothing special.
You filled the jar with liquor,
buried it,
and then burned the voodoo doll.
Yes.
It was her!
She took the item
and hid it somewhere else!
Are you saying Young Lady Qi
knew beforehand
that you were coming to search?
The facts are right in front of you.
How dare you make wild accusations?
Since that's the case,
investigate this matter thoroughly
and clear my name.
♪How I wish to hold
onto this fleeting warmth♪
♪How I wish to live
this life only for you♪
♪When memories sink
and the heart settles♪
♪Forgetting life, death,
parting, and reunion♪
♪How I wish to stay
only in the moment with you♪
♪Anchoring myself by your side♪